Mahmoud Kharouf

Land Surveyor

0566	400	00/
0566	4()()	796

Tulkarm, Baqa ash-Sharqiyya

Education

Diploma Degree

Ramallah Women's Training Center 2017 - 2019 66

Omar Bin Al Khattab S.School graduated in the year 2017

Scientific Field 60.6

Expertise

GPS

AutoCad

Microsoft Office

Language

English: Intermediate (B1 to B2 level)

Hobbies

Web Development *yelpCamp Bootcamp*

Computer Hardware and Software

About Me

During my 3-year tenure as a surveyor at a land and water settlement I have gained extensive experience working with GPS and AutoCAD. I have collaborated with task leaders and developed skillsin performing accurate field surveys.

My ability to work effectively under pressure and as a team player has been honed through my professional experiences. Additionally, my possession of a valid car license has enabled efficient on-site visits, enabling comprehensive surveys across diverse locations.

Currently ongoing studies in Computer Science (AlQuds Open University)

Work Experience

Jun 2020 - Sep 2022 Ahmad Al-Ammer I Tulkarm - Qaffin

Surveyor

Conducted land surveys in Qaffin, including buildings, using GPS devices.

July 2019 - July 2020 Thafer Al-Qaisi, Tulkarm

O Tranier

During my land surveying training, I used GPS equipment to survey land and structures. Moreover, I acquired expertise in AutoCAD and the process of obtaining building permits.

February 2019 - May 2019 Ziyad Jabarin, Ramallah

O RWTC Trainer

Apartment Guessing

I received a grade of 68.27 for my diploma in Land Surveying Comprehensive exam 69.2.

The project involved using Total Station to survey the faculty's features and implementing these features in AutoCAD.

Additionally, I used ArcMap to correct the coordinates.